原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译   AlgerDestiny  A序列  五天
翻译   马丁马丁回音山  不见动森  VC
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第十八集
不到加村不回头
线上网课
春田镇
飞兰德斯
我不能在山上写字
巴仔恶魔
欢迎来到春田镇
也许我们应该重新找个乐园
Maybe we should find a new playground.
我害怕改变
土味罗佩[内涵圣特罗佩]
一个玩的地方
看着真不错呢
Oh. This looks nice.
阴凉的树  有门的卫生间
Shady trees, bathrooms with doors
还有滑滑梯
and that loopy-loop slide
直接把你丢到软软的旧轮胎垫上
dumps you out on soft recycled tires.
是倍耐力呢
Oh, Pirellis.
看  是你的朋友哈德森
Oh, look! It's your friend Hudson.
我儿子好像真的很喜欢你女儿
My son seems to really like your daughter.
-我是考特尼  -我是马姬
- Courtney. - Marge.
-是讽刺还是复古  -只是我的名字
- Is that ironic or retro? - It's my name.
他们玩的好开心
They're having so much fun.
-她明天还能出来玩吗  -当然
- Is she free for a playdate tomorrow? - Yes.
小家伙最近有好好乖乖的表现吗
Has she been in the same room as a peanut recently?
没有
No.
我能看看她接种的疫苗吗
Can I check off her vaccinations?
结核病  百日咳  麻腮风三联疫苗
TB? DTaP? Measles-mumps-rubella?
接种了  接种了  接种了
Yes, yes, yes.
母乳还是奶瓶
Breast or bottle?
奶瓶  但我不是恶人  我可以带些曲奇
Bottle, but I'm not a monster. I can bring cookies.
白糖派  太好玩了
White sugar. That's hilarious.
我得告诉我的另一半你说的
I'll have to tell my partner you said that.
我得告诉我的另一半你嘲笑白糖派
Well, I'm gonna tell my partner you mocked white sugar.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
松饼在桌子上  侯默
Pancakes are on the table, Homie.
燕麦酥一会儿就好
And flapjacks will be ready in a few minutes.
马姬  我在减肥
Marge, I'm trying to lose weight.
松饼很可以
Pancakes will be fine.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我得面对现实  某些小地方我得放过自己
I have to face facts. In some small ways, I've let myself go.
怎么了  谁死了
What's wrong? Who died?
我们担心你会死
We're worried you will.
我们希望你长命百岁  爸比
We want you to live longer, Dad.
我就从来不这么希望
Never what I want.
行吧
Fine.
这样吧  别管松饼了
You know what, skip the pancakes.
我就只
I'll just have...
带一个葡萄柚
a grapefruit to go.
我没有亲眼看到登月  也没见证柏林墙倒塌
I didn't see the moon landing or the fall of the Berlin Wall,
我着实看见了我爸爸带了个葡萄柚
I did see my father take a grapefruit to go.
真是谢了  哥们  你让我们错失锦标赛
Thanks a lot, pal! You cost us the pennant!
就是这里
Yeah, right there!
昨天的披萨
Yesterday's pizza.
我梦里全都是你  老朋友
I have been dreaming about you my friend.
我睡觉的时候在说  "超大的饼底"
While I slept, I said, "Extra large."
但是告诉我老婆我说的是  "性感的马姬"
But I told my wife I said, "Sexy Marge."
春田核电站
下个出口
为什么我没戴吃披萨专用手套
Why didn't put on my pizza-eating gloves.
吃披萨专用手套
过肩玉米棒支架
汉堡专用手套
春田核电站
下个出口
你在哪呢  侯默
Where are you, Homer?
伯恩斯刚刚召集员工开会
Burns just called a staff meeting.
最后剩下的座位就在他旁边
The only seats are next to him.
天啊  我需要你显灵
Oh, God, I need a miracle.
不如带个气球送给同事们
Hey, why don't you bring a balloon to your coworkers?
气球
漂浮的球
他们就像不用费力放起来的风筝
They're like kites without the hard work.
你卖气球多久了
How long have you been selling balloons.
这是个有趣的故事
It's an interesting story.
*这是有着可悲故事的山里汉*
*Well, this is a story of a poor mountain man*
*英语说得比成龙先生还烂*
*Spoke worse English than Mr. Jackie Chan*
*有一天他在打理自己的酒厂*
*Then one day, he was tendin' to his still*
*听到滋滋的声音裤子被灌得满当当*
*Heard a hissing sound and his pants began to fill*
氦气  透明的黄金  符号He
Helium. See-through gold. Symbol, H-E.
*你意识到的第一件事*
*Well, the first thing you know...*
他走了  我最好的朋友走了
He's gone. My best friend is gone.
春田核电站
我想让你们知道你们以为是假人的那位同事
I want you to know that the coworker you thought was Chip Incognito
其实是我伪装的
was actually me undercover. .
抱歉各位  我来晚了
Sorry I am late everybody.
给  拿个气球
Here, have a balloon.
辛普森  伯恩斯先生是财富排名前500的CEO
Simpson, Mr. Burns is a Fortune 500 CEO.
他是不会...
He's not going to...
安静  你个傻子
Quiet, you fool.
纯净未稀释的氦气
Pure, uncut helium.
多亏了生日气球  让此气球更弥足珍贵
Thanks to birthday balloons, rarer than ever.
史密瑟斯  我提醒你一下  我们花了一大笔钱
Smithers, might I remind you we pay a fortune
购买氦气冷却反应堆
for helium to cool our reactors?
您还是一如既往的正确
Right as always, sir.
一如既往地正确  先生
价格高上天
That price is sky-high!
你在哪里得到的气球
Where did you get this?
我从乡巴佬那里买到的  他有好多
Oh, the bumpkin I got it from has tons of it.
但是我要提醒你
But I got to warn you...
他完全不知道这东西的价值
he has no idea of what it's worth.
太好了
Excellent.
我喜欢精心设计的骗局
How I love a good swindle.
你认为呢
What do you think?
他叫我说话
He called on me!
至于你  辛普森  获得了月度最佳员工称号
As for you, Simpson, Employee of the Month.
月度最佳员工
马姬  我今天在会议上的表现秒杀全场
So, Marge, I killed it at the staff meeting today.
诀窍是准备到位
The key is preparation.
在阿麦身上有惊喜的事情发生
Something amazing has happened to Maggie.
她恋爱了
She's in love.
如果这个再可爱点  我就要沦陷了
If this gets any cuter, I'm gonna bust.
克里塔斯  去看看谁在敲门
Cletus, get the dang door!
拿着一把没上膛的枪可照顾不好客人
I can't very well answer the door with an unloaded shotgun,
对吗  女人
Can I, woman?
你好啊  邻居
Howdy, neighbor.
要不要来点曼哈顿松鼠杂烩
May I offer you some Manhattan squirrel chowder?
你闻起来像是在楼房居住
You smell like indoor plumbin'.
他发现我们了
He's onto us.
我们没必要再装成乡巴佬的样子
No need to pretend we're inbred hicks.
无意冒犯  先生
No offense, goober.
没事的
None taken.
斯帕科勒  我想要你的氦气
All right, Spuckler. You've got helium, which I want.
我有你想要的东西
I've got what you want,
一瓶装满了十美分硬币的锡罐
a tin cup filled with dimes.
我们来做个交易
Let's make a deal.
等一下
Now, hold on.
我做辛苦的交易之前
I likes to have a drink with a feller
想找人喝一杯
beforen I make a busy-ness deal.
我尝遍所有有毒的东西
I have imbibed every intoxicant
密歇根州的弗林特市水源曾遭到铅污染
从甜耶鲁啤酒到密歇根的弗林特水源
from sweet Yale beer to Flint, Michigan water.
放马过来吧
Do your worst.
一点事情也没有
lutely no effect upon my...
先生  也许这个叫斯帕科勒的家伙
Sir, maybe this Spuckler fellow
比我们想象的要聪明一点
is a little smarter than we thought.
胡说
Nonsense.
也许我们可以用傻瓜来抓住傻瓜
Perhaps it takes an idiot to catch an idiot.
您好  有人能帮我吗  我的三明治在这里丢的
Hello! Could I get a little help? I dropped my sandwich in here.
你和斯帕科勒将会得到人们常说的
You and Mr. Spuckler will enter into what the hoi polloi called a
友谊
"Friendship,"
然后利用这友情
then use that friendship to destroy his life
由内而外毁掉他的生活
from the inside out.
不好吧  他还有孩子
I don't know. He's got kids.
我不想骗一家人损失他们的家园
I can't cheat a family out of their home.
但欺骗我不要夺取他们的家
But you're perfectly fine
你就觉得没什么问题
cheating me out of their home.
你想迷惑我
Oh. You're trying to confuse me.
我要溜了  陷阱门去哪了
I got to get out. Where's the trap door?
救救我
Save me.
财务室的温斯坦  你认识的
You know Weinstein from Accounting.
要是你觉得困惑
If you're confused,
或许这两位能帮你清醒一下
perhaps these two gentlemen can clarify things.
这位喜欢制造痛苦
This fellow loves inflicting pain.
这位则喜欢在另一位制造痛苦的时候
And this fellow loves to laugh while he watches
在一边站着大笑
this one produce the pain.
你是制造痛苦的那个  还是大笑的那个
Are you the pain guy or the laugh guy?
问你话呢
Answer the question.
有人吗  阿麦来参加玩耍聚会了
Hello? Maggie Simpson here for a playdate.
哈德森正在开电话会议
Hudson's on a conference call.
我帮你开门
I'll buzz you in.
你的家真漂亮
You have a lovely home.
地板是什么材质
What is this floor made out of?
是一座威尼斯教堂的瓷砖
The tile was a Venetian church
我们把它拆除  用小船运了回来
which we dismantled, shipped over by small boat
再由99岁高龄的贝聿铭精心安装
and had lovingly installed by a 99-year-old I.M. Pei.
听着好贵
That sounds pricey.
不  卫生间的装修才叫贵
No, the toilet is pricey.
我们雇的水管工效率太低了
The plumbers we hired to replace it are very inefficient.
再使点劲  你们这群小矮子
Let's go, you little runts.
怎么  尿布满了吗
What? Are your diapers full?
你填这份性史表的时候想来点咖啡吗
Would you like some coffee as you fill out a sexual history?
性史表
Sexual history?
然后我们的宝宝才能成为朋友吗
So our babies can be friends?
这里是我的
Here's mine.
好
All right.
加奶  不加糖
Cream, no sugar.
性史表
只有侯默
现在已经很少看到婴儿用奶嘴了
So unusual to see a baby with a pacifier these days.
婴儿杀手剂
你宝宝的头发好有趣哦
Your baby has such interesting hair.
你不介意我给她装上保护措施
You don't mind that I babyproofed your baby
-来保护我的宝宝对吧  -我介意
- from my baby, do you? - Yes, I do.
很介意
Very much.
阿麦  我们走  赶紧的
Maggie, let's go. Now.
而且我们不会再回来了
And we're not coming back.
斯帕科勒家
兄弟干嘛呢
Whatcha doing there, friend?
又见面啦
Good to see you again.
是个男孩
犹太女孩受诫礼
-好的 -好的
- A-yup. - A-yup.
"好的"就完事儿了
Nothing like a good "a-yup"
-能让人放松下来  -好的
- to put a man at ease. - A-yup.
-好的  -好的
- A-yup. - A-yup.
-好的  -不好
- A-yup. - A-nope.
我是说  好的
I mean, a-yup.
朋友
Say, friend,
我看到你用嘴吸氦气再吐到
looks like you're working awful hard
聚酯薄膜气球里挺费劲的
to suck the helium into them thar Mylar balloons.
可不  累惨了
Oh, it's powerful tiresome.
但上帝既然把氦气埋在我家地下
But the Lord done put helium under my feet,
我就不能让它白白飘散
and I must not spill it into the sky.
现在听着
Now, listen.
跟他说你有办法让他活得更轻松
Explain that you have a way to make his life easier.
假装是你的主意
Pretend it's your idea.
他是能相信你会有主意的那种傻瓜
He's stupid enough to believe you have an idea.
就说"要是我说我知道一个办法
Say, "What if I told you
能轻松收集这天赐的氦气呢"
there was a way to harvest that noble gas?"
"要是我说我知道一个办法
"What if I told you there was a way
能轻松收集这天赐的氦气呢
to harvest that noble gas
不需要你嘴费劲
without the strain on your mouth puffer."
我会说  "切"
I'd say, "Aw, pshaw,"
然后让你"继续"
but then I'd follow it with a "Go on."
很好
Excellent.
"很好"
"Excellent."
不  别说很好
No, don't say excellent.
"不  别说很好"
"No, don't say excellent."
这句也别说
No, don't say that, either.
"这句也别说"
"No, don't say that, either."
你闭嘴吧
Just shut up.
"你闭嘴吧"
"Just shut up."
我会考虑你的建议
I'll have to mull your proposal,
特别是最后那句
especially that last crazy part.
省了不少活啊
You just saved me a passel of work.
现在我有空生更多孩子了
Now I can spend more time making more family.
侯默·杰·辛普森
Homer J. Simpson.
克里塔斯·德尔洛伊·蒙特福特·比格沃斯·斯帕科勒
Cletus Delroy Montfort Bigglesworth Spuckler.
现在咱去那头
Now, let's go yonder
抓点鲶鱼吧
and get ourselves a mess of catfish.
我把胳膊深深插进鲇鱼洞里
All right, I'm gonna get my arm so deep into that catfish hole,
就会有傻鲶鱼上钩
that ole chucklehead just bites my bone.
小菜一碟
Easy-peasy.
别吓到它  会让鱼肉变酸
Now, don't scare him. It sours up the flavor.
它在舔我的眼睛
It's licking my eye.
死了吗
Is it dead?
谢谢你
Thank you.
没有什么比斯帕科勒家传统炸鱼宴更好了
All right, nothing like a good ole Spuckler family fish fry.
主啊  谢谢你把这个
Dear Lord, thank you for bringing
没毛的沼泽猛兽带给我们
this hairless swamp beast our way.
他对于您神秘气球气的智慧
His wisdom regarding your mystery balloon gas
帮助我们斯帕科勒一家有了两台收音机
has helped us Spucklers become a two-radio family.
侯默  我想做你的合作伙伴
Homer, I want to be your partner.
交个杯来成交吧  来吧
Seal the deal with a hillbilly handshake. Come on.
我现在也把你当家人了
I consider you family now,
其实也没多少人好选
which is not really that select a circle.
负鼠意面
-很好  -哪里来的声音
- Excellent. - Where'd that come from?
干得好  辛普森  我们会夺走他的一切
Well done, Simpson. We'll take him for everything
除了草坪上的沙发
except the couch on his lawn.
但我们是一家人了
Well, but we're family.
你就不能整他个半死吗
Couldn't you just screw him half over?
整人不能只整个半死
No one screws anyone half over.
就像是只拿十亿美元的一半  有意义吗
It's like having half a billion dollars. What's the point of that?
怎么了
What's up?
我觉得我们都不开心  但我担心你会先说
I think we're both upset, but I'm worried you're gonna talk first.
不  你先说
No, you go ahead.
我要整死一个对我非常好的家伙
I'm supposed to screw over a guy that's only been nice to me.
我让阿麦开心不起来
I'm denying Maggie happiness
就因为我受不了她朋友的妈
because I can't stand the mother of her friend.
阿麦没事的
Maggie'll be fine.
我才刚跟她一起玩了
I just played with her.
她还以为我拿了她的鼻子
She still thinks I've got her nose.
等下  我放哪里去了
Wait, where'd I put it?
不在这里
Not here.
不  不在
No. No.
看看你找到了什么
Look what you found.
哈德森周岁典礼
有些事我得告诉你
I have something I need to tell you.
哈德森办了个生日派对
Hudson had a birthday party,
但是我没告诉你  你就错过了
but I didn't tell you, so you missed it.
我可以解释
I can explain.
他的妈妈太讨人厌了
That other mom was just so annoying
她有什么空中绸带  还有瑜伽裤
with her aerial silks and those yoga pants.
她做普拉提  又不是瑜伽
She does Pilates, not yoga.
她让我自惭形秽
She made me feel bad about myself.
你明白的  对吧  对吧
You get it, right? Right?
让他把这合同签了  辛普森
Get this contract signed, Simpson.
不然呢
Or what?
或许你该稍微尝尝等着你的东西
Perhaps you need a little taste of what's in store.
抱歉了  史密瑟斯
Sorry, Smithers.
我们不想留一个克里塔斯能看见的印子
We didn't want to leave a mark that Cletus could see.
但是你本来可以先警告我一下
But you could've warned me first.
说得对  小心身后
Fair enough. Watch your back.
这不是我全世界
Well, if it ain't my bestest friend
最好的朋友吗
on God's flat Earth.
你手里拿的什么
So, what's in your hand?
是我们友谊的证明吗
Some sort of a friendship certificate?
你懂的  只是
Uh, you know, just something
让我们的合作关系更进一步的协议
to put our partnership on the up-and-up.
有什么比氦气生意更棒的吗
Hey, what's more up-and-up than the helium business?
你不打算先读一下吗
Ain't you gonna read it?
我相信你  像小羊羔相信友善的大灰狼一样
I trust you, like a sheep trusts a friendly wolf.
我要签个X
I signs with an "X"
因为我的手机是iPhone X
'cause that's the kind of iPhone I got.
第二笔写完  协议就正式生效了
And now for the second slash that makes it official.
我需要一把直尺
Oh, I need a straightedge.
直尺  过来  儿子
Straight-Edge! Get over here, boy!
来了  爸爸
Yes, Daddy.
我不能这么做
I can't do it.
你让我的笔飘走了
You done floated my mark-maker.
我不会让你签的
I won't let you sign it.
这协议是骗取你的氦气的骗局
It's all a trick to steal your helium.
你竟然想从二十九个孩子的爹身上骗钱吗
You was gonna steal from a man what has 29 kids?
30个  31个
30, 31!
但我及时制止了你
Yeah, but I told you before it was too late.
好吧  还是好朋友
Okay, we're still buddies.
因为城里人撒谎而生气
Getting mad at city folk for lying is like
就像因为你六岁的女儿没护理枪
getting mad ‭Okaat your six-year-oldes.
而大发雷霆一样可笑
for not cleaning her gun.
-握个手吧  -你伸的是左手
-Put her there. -Uh, that's your left hand.
我两只都是左手
They's both left hands.
辛普森  你这蠢货
Simpson, you fool.
希望你今早和你妻子的吻别足够温馨
I hope you kissed your wife well this morning,
因为以后你再也没机会了
because it will be the last one.
只是个中规中矩的吻
Well, it was a medium.
不小心亲到她耳朵了
Part of it hit her ear.
你们要是敢伤害我的朋友
Hey, you harm my friend,
就别想从我这拿到球里的一颗氦气
you ain't getting balloon one of my helium.
永远别想
And I mean ever.
别绕来绕去了
Quite the dilemma.
史密瑟斯  不想挨踢的话就把这事给我摆平
Smithers, solve this if you don't want another kick.
克里塔斯  关于你的氦气
Cletus, about your helium.
如果我们出个合理[集市]的价格呢
What if we paid you a fair price?
乡村集市还是州集市
County fair or state fair?
我不能输给这么蠢的人
I can't lose to someone so stupid.
打手们  解决他
Goons, get him.
我们会付给你钱的
We'll pay you what's right.
成交
We have a deal.
回头联系我家的猎狗商讨细节
Have your people call my basset hound.
这能让你忘记你那些亿万富翁的烦恼
Well, this'll help you forget your billionaire troubles.
来吸一口吧  朋友
Have a toke on this, friend.
救命  救命
Help me! Help me!
你会后悔的
You'll rue the day.
史密瑟斯  电线
Smithers, power lines!
阿麦  你还太小  不该在痛苦中度过余生
Oh, Maggie. You're too young to be miserable the rest of your life.
在这部爱情喜剧中  我不会是个刻薄的母亲
In this rom-com, I am not going to be the mean mother.
我们走吧
Let's go.
土味罗佩
一个玩耍的地方
知道吗  我们的共同点就是
You know, the one thing we have in common
我们愿意为了孩子装作喜欢对方
is we're willing to pretend that we like each other for our children.
对此  我想说  "亲亲"
To that, I say, "Kiss-kiss."
*我们在分享粗玉米粥*
*Ooh, we're sharing some grits*
*你的加了黄油  我的加了负鼠肉汁*
*Yours has butter, mine has possum gravy*
*我们是哥们  所以我会吃你的奇怪食物*
*We're pals, so I eat your weird food*
*你让我长胖了  侯默*
*Ooh, you're making me fat now, Homer*
*我活不久了*
*I don't have long to live*
气球
会漂浮的球
*你是我有过的*
*Ooh, you're the best friend*
*最好的朋友  是你*
*That I ever had, you're the one*
*让我的气球在空中漂浮*
*Who keeps my balloons flying*
*你是我的私藏佳酿*
*You're my moonshine*
*而且我想让你知道*
*And I want you to know*
*我不是在嗅胶水*
*That I'm not sniffing glue*
有微量致幻兴奋物质
*我真的很爱你*
*I really love you*
不含酒精
*你是我最好的朋友*
*Oh, you're my best friend*
*你给了我你的牙齿*
*Ooh, you gave me your tooth*
*你在给我削凳子  我真开心*
*I love that you're whittlin' a stool for me*
*我要两个  每个屁股墩一个*
*I need two, one for each cheek*
*两个  下周你就能拿到  侯默*
*Two, you'll have 'em next week, now, Homer*
*真好  我们往小溪里撒尿吧*
*Cool, let's pee in the creek*
*你就是个乡下人*
*Ooh, you're a mountain man*
*依靠田野为生*
*Who lives off the grid*
*你端着猎枪赶走了伯恩斯*
*You chased off Burns with a shotgun*
*那可真好玩*
*That was such fun*
*我爱喝*
*And I love to drink*
*你蒸馏出来的甲醇*
*The methanol from your still*
*你是我最好的朋友*
*Ooh, you're my best friend*
*我可能活不成了*
*Ooh, I might not live*
*你是我最好的朋友*
*Ooh, you're my best friend*